(Raj:)Or totally naked.
I love Howard,
(Raj:)but the dude needs
a little shame.
(Sheldon:)All right, Amy, this
walkie-talkie is yours.
(Sheldon:)If we run into any problems,
I'll contact you.
(Sheldon:)And if anything bad happens,
what's the rule?
(Amy:)Save you first; come back
for Raj only if there's time.
(Raj:)We're going
to be fine.
(exhales)
Sheldon, I'm really impressed
(Amy:)you're willing to try this.
(Sheldon:)Well, admittedly,
this brushes up
(Sheldon:)against my well-known aversions
to heat, small places,
(Sheldon:)going below floor-level,
(Sheldon:)dampness, hatches,
ladders,
(Sheldon:)darkness, echoes,
(Sheldon:)and eliminating in
Home Depot buckets.
(Sheldon:)That last one is quite new,
but I have a feeling
(Sheldon:)that's gonna rocket
to the top of the list.
KOOTHRAPPALI (grunts):
I'm sweating already.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, as the person beneath you,
allow me to say, I know.